{
    "subject": "resource/Farouk_al-Sharaa",
    "predicate": "ontology/office",
    "object": "Minister of Foreign Affairs",
    "human_readable": "Farouk al-Sharaa held the office of Minister of Foreign Affairs.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9657224416732788,
            "question": "Who succeeded Farouk al-Sharaa as Minister of Foreign Affairs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9525686502456665,
            "question": "Were there any significant events during Farouk al-Sharaa's tenure as Minister of Foreign Affairs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8950420618057251,
            "question": "What office did Farouk al-Sharaa hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8404269218444824,
            "question": "Who was Farouk al-Sharaa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6861798167228699,
            "question": "How did Farouk al-Sharaa's policies impact international relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6060783267021179,
            "question": "What country was Farouk al-Sharaa likely associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5877285599708557,
            "question": "In what capacity did Farouk al-Sharaa serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5441043972969055,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Farouk al-Sharaa's political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.509331464767456,
            "question": "What is the role of a Minister of Foreign Affairs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43529996275901794,
            "question": "What were some of the challenges faced by Farouk al-Sharaa in his role?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Farouk al-Sharaa held the office of Minister of Foreign Affairs.",
            "html": "dbpedia_792_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the role of a Minister of Foreign Affairs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_792_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Farouk al-Sharaa's political career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_792_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what capacity did Farouk al-Sharaa serve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_792_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_792_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because, according to the documents provided, Farouk al-Sharaa served as foreign minister of Syria from 1984 until 2006 when he became Vice President of Syria. He was appointed again as Minister of Foreign Affairs in February 2006, after a cabinet reshuffle."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Farouk al-Sharaa held the office of Minister of Foreign Affairs.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention Farouk al-Sharaa serving in this position during different periods. For instance, one document states: \"Sharaa still holds the vice-presidency,\" and another mentions him as \"Syria\u2019s Minister of Foreign Affairs in 1984,\" later he was also appointed as \"minister of foreign affairs on 11 February 2006.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}